[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":53585,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":613104,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure th at when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":11298,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":624403,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":16387,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":640791,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2263,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":643055,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":5870,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":648926,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2082,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":651009,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the seco nd one t o it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":9285,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":660295,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1802,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":662097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3345,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":665442,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1512,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":666955,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3896,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":670851,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub >6</sub>  0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1532,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":672383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5950,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":678334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1371,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":679705,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br  /><br />  (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":5057,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":684763,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1080,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":685844,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your re sult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4377,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":690222,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1431,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":691654,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3275,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":694929,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1091,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":696021,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":6109,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":702130,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":2043,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":704173,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":26928,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":731102,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own in verse un der +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":53158,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":784263,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":12182,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":796446,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1400,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":797847,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br  /><br / > (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":4286,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":802134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2172,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":804306,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3715,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":808022,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1332,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":809354,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2844,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":812198,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity und er +<sub >6</sub>.","rt":1351,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":813549,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3185,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":816735,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":10140,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":826876,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can si mply be  performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":67881,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":894758,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</ sub> 2,  but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":108055,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":1002814,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":7554,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1010372,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":2992,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1013365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br / ><br />  (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":3744,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1017109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":17547,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1034658,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<su b>6</sub >? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":18285,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1052947,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":2311,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1055258,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4534,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1059793,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1440,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1061234,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with fee dback to  make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":35607,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1096844,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4578,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1101422,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1471,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1102893,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":4134,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1107028,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":11501,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1118530,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":9220,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1127751,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9","0"],"rt":13705,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1141456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":12459,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1153915,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":16633,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1170549,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"I added the two numbers and the answer was not 9 or greater so that is the final number.","explanation_history":["I added the two numbers and they were not grea","I added the two numbers and they were not gre","I added the two numbers and they were not gr","I added the two numbers and they were not g","I added the two numbers and they were not 9 or greater so that is the answer.","I added the two numbers and the  not 9 or greater so that is the answer.","I added the two numbers and the a not 9 or greater so that is the answer.","I added the two numbers and the an not 9 or greater so that is the answer.","I added the two numbers and the ans not 9 or greater so that is the answer.","I added the two numbers and the answe not 9 or greater so that is the answer.","I added the two n umbers a nd the answer not 9 or greater so that is the answer.","I added the two numbers and the answer  not 9 or greater so that is the answer.","I added the two numbers and the answer w not 9 or greater so that is the answer.","I added the two numbers and the answer ws not 9 or greater so that is the answer.","I added the two numbers and the answer w not 9 or greater so that is the answer.","I added the two numbers and the answer wa not 9 or greater so that is the answer.","I added the two numbers and the answer was not 9 or greater so that is the answer.","I added the two numbers and the answer was not 9 or greater so that is the f.","I added the two numbers and the answer was not 9 or greater so that is the fi.","I added the two numbers and the answer was not 9 or greater so that is the fin.","I added the two numbers and the answer was not 9 or greater so that is the fina.","I added the two numbers and the answer was not 9 or greater so that is the final.","I added the two number s and th e answer was not 9 or greater so that is the final .","I added the two numbers and the answer was not 9 or greater so that is the final n.","I added the two numbers and the answer was not 9 or greater so that is the final nu.","I added the two numbers and the answer was not 9 or greater so that is the final num.","I added the two numbers and the answer was not 9 or greater so that is the final numb.","I added the two numbers and the answer was not 9 or greater so that is the final number."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":43679,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1214229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"8+4=12 and 12 is greater than 9 so I subtract 9. 12-9=3","explanation_history":["8+4=12 and 12 is greater than 9 so I subtraf","8+4=12  and 12 i s greater than 9 so I subtract 9. 12-9=3"],"response_history":["3"],"rt":42730,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1256960,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"The identity under 9 would be 0 because 9+0=9 and 9-9=0.","explanation_history":["8+1","8+","8","The identity under 9 would be -","The identity under 9 would be 0 because 9+0=9-","The identity under 9 would be 0 because 9+0=9 and 9-9=)","The identity under 9 would be 0 because 9+0=9 and 9-9=0."],"response_history":["1","0"],"rt":106831,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1363792,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":12734,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1376529,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":10317,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1386846,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":2732,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1389578,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +< sub>9</s ub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"3+6=9 and 9-9=0 so 6 would be the inverse of 3.","explanation_history":["6+3=9 and 9-9=0 so 6 would be the inverse of 3","8=9 and 9-9=0 so 6 would be the inverse of 3","=9 and 9-9=0 so 6 would be the inverse of 3","3=9 and 9-9=0 so 6 would be the inverse of 3","3+=9 and 9-9=0 so 6 would be the inverse of 3","3+6=9 and 9-9=0 so 6 would be the inverse of 3."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":41055,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1430634,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=4+2=6, 2+2+2 +2=4+2+2 =6+2=8. You are still missing 2,5,7,9.","explanation_history":["You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For exap","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2_","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 22+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+22+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=2+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=42+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4,2+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 22+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+22+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the  numbers  using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+22+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 22+2+2=4+2=6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=4+2=6, 2+2+2+2=4+2+2=6+2=8. You are still missing 2,5,6,7","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=4+2=6, 2+2+2+2=4+2+2=6+2=8. You are still missing 2,5,6,","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=4+2=6, 2+2+2+2=4+2+2=6+2=8. You are still missing 2,5,6","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=4+2=6, 2+2+2+2=4+2+2=6+2=8. You are still missing 2,5,7 and","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=4+2=6, 2+2+2+2=4+2+2=6+2=8. You are still missing 2,5,7 an","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=4+2=6, 2+2+2+2=4+ 2+2=6+2= 8. You are still missing 2,5,7 a","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=4+2=6, 2+2+2+2=4+2+2=6+2=8. You are still missing 2,5,7 ","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=4+2=6, 2+2+2+2=4+2+2=6+2=8. You are still missing 2,5,7, 9","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=4+2=6, 2+2+2+2=4+2+2=6+2=8. You are still missing 2,5,7, ","You cannot get all the numbers using 2. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=4+2=6, 2+2+2+2=4+2+2=6+2=8. You are still missing 2,5,7,9."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":135147,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1565782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3. For example, 3+3 =6, 3+3+ 3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3+3=6+3+3+3+3=0+3+3+3=3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0. It just keeps repeating itself and all you get are 0 or 3.","explanation_history":["3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3","3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0,3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3","3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, =3=3=","3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, =3=3","3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, =3=","3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, =3+3+3","3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","Y3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You 3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You c3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You ca3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You can3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cann3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You canno3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0,  3+3+3+3= 6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot 3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot g3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get 3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get al3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all 3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all th3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the 3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the n3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the nu3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the num3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3 =3, 3+3+ 3+3+3","You cannot get all the numb3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbe3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers 3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers wh3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when 3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when a3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when ad3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when add3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when addin3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+ 3=0+3=3,  3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding 3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 33+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3.3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3. 3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3. F3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3. For3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when addin g up 3.  For 3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3. For e3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3. For ex3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3. For exa3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3. For exam3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3. For examp3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3. For exampl3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3. For example3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3. For example,3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3","You cannot g et all t he numbers when adding up 3. For example, 3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3+3=6+3+3+3+3=0+3+3+3=3+3+3=6+3=9-9=)","You cannot get all the numbers when adding up 3. For example, 3+3=6, 3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0, 3+3+3+3=6+3+3=0+3=3, 3+3+3+3+3+3=6+3+3+3+3=0+3+3+3=3+3+3=6+3=9-9=0. It just keeps repeating itself and all you get are 0 or 3."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":184217,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1750005,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For example, 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2, 5+5+5+5+5=1+5+5+5+5=6+5+5+5=2+5+5=7+5=12-9=3 and so on. ","explanation_history":["5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","Y5+5=10-9=1, 5+5 +5=1+5=6 , 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You c5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You ca5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can g5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get a5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get al5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all o5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of th5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5 =6+5=11- 9=2,","You can get all of the 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the n5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the nu5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the num5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numb5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbe5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the number5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers b5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You  can get  all of the numbers by si5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by sim5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simp5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simpl5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply a5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply ad5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply addi5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply addin5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5 =1+5=6,  5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 55+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5.5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. F5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. Fo5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For e5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all  of the n umbers by simply adding 5. For ex5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For exam5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For examp5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For exampl5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For example5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For example,5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For example, 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For example, 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2,5+5+5=1+5=6, ,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For example, 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9 =2, 5+5+ 5=1+5=6, ,","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For example, 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2, 5+5+5=1+5=6, ","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For example, 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2, 5+5+5=1+5=6, 5+5+5+5+5=1+5+5+5+5=6+5+5+5=2+5+5=7+5=12-9=3","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For example, 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2, 5+5+5+5+5=1+5+5+5+5=6+5+5+5=2+5+5=7+5=12-9=3  ","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For example, 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2, 5+5+5+5+5=1+5+5+5+5=6+5+5+5=2+5+5=7+5=12-9=3 an ","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For example, 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2, 5+5+5+5+5=1+5+5+5+5=6+5+5+5=2+5+5=7+5=12-9=3 and  ","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For example, 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2, 5+5+5+5+5=1+5+5+5+5=6+5+5+5=2+5+5=7+5=12-9=3 and so  ","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For example, 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5 +5+5=1+5 +5=6+5=11-9=2, 5+5+5+5+5=1+5+5+5+5=6+5+5+5=2+5+5=7+5=12-9=3 and so on ","You can get all of the numbers by simply adding 5. For example, 5+5=10-9=1, 5+5+5+5=1+5+5=6+5=11-9=2, 5+5+5+5+5=1+5+5+5+5=6+5+5+5=2+5+5=7+5=12-9=3 and so on. "],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":191784,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1941795,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"You cannot get all the numbers by adding 6 together.","explanation_history":["You cannont g","You cannont ","You cannont","You cannon","You canno","You cannot get all numbers by adding 5","You cannot get all numbers by adding 6 together.","You cannot get all  numbers by adding 6 together.","You cannot get all th numbers by adding 6 together.","You cannot get all the n umbers b y adding 6 together."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":77356,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2019155,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":34752,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2053909,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":23971,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2077881,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x+x","explain":true,"explanation":"I'm not exactly sure what you are looking for here. If we don't know what n means, then I'm not sure how we know what the inverse of x is. I guessed x+x because if you add two of the same number together and then subtracted it, then you'll get the same number.","explanation_history":["I'm not exactly sure what you are looking for here. If we don't know what n means, then I'm not sure wh","I'm not exactly sure what you are looking for here. If we don't know what n means, then I'm not sure w","I'm not exactly sure what you are looking for here. If we don't know what n means, then I'm not sure how we n","I'm not exactly sure what you are looking for here. If we don't know what n means, then I'm no t sure h ow we know what the inverse of x is. I guessed x+x because if you add two of the same m","I'm not exactly sure what you are looking for here. If we don't know what n means, then I'm not sure how we know what the inverse of x is. I guessed x+x because if you add two of the same number together and then subtracted it, then you'll ge thte ","I'm not exactly sure what you are looking for here. If we don't know what n means, then I'm not sure how we know what the inverse of x is. I guessed x+x because if you add two of the same number together and then subtracted it, then you'll ge thte","I'm not exactly sure what you are looking for here. If we don't know what n means, then I'm not sure how we know what the inverse of x is. I guessed x+x because if you add two of the same number together and then subtracted it, then you'll ge tht","I'm not exactly sure what you are looking for here. If we don't know what n means, then I'm not sure how we know what the inverse of x is. I guessed  x+x beca use if you add two of the same number together and then subtracted it, then you'll ge th","I'm not exactly sure what you are looking for here. If we don't know what n means, then I'm not sure how we know what the inverse of x is. I guessed x+x because if you add two of the same number together and then subtracted it, then you'll ge t","I'm not exactly sure what you are looking for here. If we don't know what n means, then I'm not sure how we know what the inverse of x is. I guessed x+x because if you add two of the same number together and then subtracted it, then you'll ge ","I'm not exactly sure what you are looking for here. If we don't know what n means, then I'm not sure how we know what the inverse of x is. I guessed x+x because if you add two of the same number together and then subtracted it, then you'll get the same number."],"response_history":["x+n","x+","x+x"],"rt":111142,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2189024,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm not sure if there is a pattern or not. It seems like generators tend to be odd numbers when the +n is an odd number and then tend to be even numbers when +n is an even number.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I'm not sure if ther i","I'm not sure if ther ","I'm not sure if there is a pattern or not. It seems like generators tend to be odd numbers when the +n is odd","I'm not sure if there is a pattern or not. It seems like generators tend to be odd numbers when the +n is od","I'm not sure if there is a pattern or not. It seems like generators tend to be odd numbers when the +n is o","I'm not sure if there is a pattern or not. It seems like gen erators  tend to be odd numbers when the +n is an odd number and then tend to be even numbers when +n is an even number."],"rt":62852,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2251879,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":17149,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2269032,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":5951,"trial_type":"question ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2274983,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":24212,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2299195,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"I don't really understand the question. What is a multiple of a divisor? I'm going to guess false because we don't know what n is .","explanation_history":["I don't really understand the question. I guess it would be false because a generator can still be a multiple","I don't really understand the question. I","I don't really understand the question. What is a multiple of a diva","I don't really understand the question. What is a multiple of a divisor? I ","I don't really understand the question. What is a multiple of a divisor? I'm going to guess false because we don't know what n is."],"response_history":["False"],"rt":90794,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2389991,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":62957,"trial_type":"ques tion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2452955,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Always","explain":true,"explanation":"If X is a generator, then it would have to be a generator under x+nx. If it wasn't, then it wouldn't be a generator under x+nx.","explanation_history":["A generator has two numbers that add up to be","A ","A","X +n X is the definition of a generator - isn't it? for ","X +n X is the definition of a generator - isn't it? for","X +n X is the definition of a generator - isn't it? fo","X +n X is the definition of a generator - isn't it? f","X +n X is the definition of a generator - isn't it? For example, 2+N","X +n X is the definition  of a gen erator - isn't it? For example, 2+n2 would equal","If X is a generator, then it would have to be a generator under x+nX. ","If X is a generator, then it would have to be a generator under x+nX.","If X is a generator, then it would have to be a generator under x+nX","If X is a generator, then it would have to be a generator under x+nx. If it wasn't, then it wouldn't be a generator under x+nx."],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":135069,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2588028,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":52315,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2640348,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2869,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2643219,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"32","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["32"],"rt":2620,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2645841,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":3440,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2649281,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Advanced Calculus","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Advanced Calculus ","Advanced Calculus"],"rt":28009,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2677290,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, reme mber and  understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":19152,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2696444,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":5180,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2701624,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":3489,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2705114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3647,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2708762,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewh at","3 -  definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":3502,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2712265,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2259,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2714525,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":4519,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2719045,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":5460,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2724506,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The directions were a little confusing. I wasn't really sure what a generator was. I tried to answer the questions the best I could. It was a great HIT and I enjoyed doing it. Thanks!","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["The directions were a little confusing. I wasn't really sure what a generator was and ","The directions were a little confusing. I wasn't really sure what  a genera tor was and","The directions were a little confusing. I wasn't really sure what a generator was an","The directions were a little confusing. I wasn't really sure what a generator was a","The directions were a little confusing. I wasn't really sure what a generator was ","The directions were a little confusing. I wasn't really sure what a generator was ","The directions were a little confusing. I wasn't really sure what a generator was so ","The directions were a little confusing. I wasn't really sure what a generator was so","The directions were a little confusing. I wasn't really sure what a generator was s","The directions were a little confusing. I wasn't really sure what a generator was ","The directions were a little confusing. I wasn't really sure what a generator was. I tried to answer the questions the best I could. It was a great HIT and I enjoyed doin ","The directions were a little confusing. I wasn't really sure what a generator was. I tried to answer the questio ns the b est I could. It was a great HIT and I enjoyed doing it. Thanks!"],"rt":46265,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":2770772,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]